A Guide to the Memorabilia FA437
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1
  - National Baptist Layman Award, Antioch Baptist Church of Brooklyn, 1962 October 21; 17.25 x 14.25, DEFRAMED (Object 159)
  - Certificate presented to the Tenny Press & NAR, by Metropolitan New York, 29th Exhibition of Printing for "1970 Nonmedia Campaign", 1971; 17 x 14, see #222, 651 (Object 159)
  - Honorary Membership, Water Pollution Control Federation, 1974; 14 x 17 (Object 160)
  - Award, National Association of State Labor Relations Agencies, 1962 September; 17 x 14 (Object 161)
  - wood carving "Instituto Nacional de Proteccion a la Infancia", 1969 May 12; 17 x 15.75 (Object 163)
  - Resolution by U.S. Senate concerning restoration, signed by NAR, 1976 May 16; 17.25 x 24, see #212 (Object 163)
  - picture of NAR & Kissinger, artist Sydney Cash, from Arthur Rashap, 1975 April 16; 15 x 12, DEFRAMED (Object 164, Box 43)
  - Honorary membership, Alpha Zeta at Cornell, 8.5 x 10, DEFRAMED; see #734, 810 (Object 165, Box 90)
  - Kappa Delta Sigma Fraternity membership, NYS Agri/Tech Institute, 1966 October 6; 9.25 x 11.75, DEFRAMED (Object 166, Box 90)
  - honorary doctorate, Manhattan College, 1968 March 20; 20 x 25.5, see # 467 for related speech (Object 168)
  - commission as Kentucky Colonel, State of Kentucky, 1976 February 4; see #571 for related (Object 168)
  - Silver Beaver Award, Boy Scouts of America, 1959 July 28; 14 x 18, see # 122 for list; DEFRAMED (Object 170)
  - Urban Transportation Award, Pittsburgh Urban Transit Council, 1968 March 12; 18.5 x 14.5 (Object 170)
  - Distinguished Service Award, Women's National Republican Club, 1973 March 10; 12.75 x 16.75, see #s 115, 76 for related (Object 171)
  - NAR addressing convention, possibly 89th ANPA Convention, 14.5 x 18.25, DEFRAMED (Object 173)
  - Eugene Ormandy, signed, 1966 August; 12.75 x 15.75, taken in Philadelphia (Object 174)
  - Award, Jewish Teachers Association, 1970 September 6; 15 x 12, DEFRAMED (Object 175, Box 90)
  - commendation from National Chairman of Jobs for Veterans, 14 x 11, see #609; DEFRAMED (Object 175, Box 90)
  - Award, Grand St. Boys Post 1025 of American Legion, 1957 November 11; 15 x 12, see #s 411, 414; DEFRAMED (Object 177, Box 90)
  - decree, American Society for Friendship with Switzerland Inc, 1966; 8 x 13, DEFRAMED (Object 177, Box 90)
  - certificate, Oregon Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1964 February 8; 13 x 11, DEFRAMED (Object 178, Box 90)
  - honorary life membership, Building Industry Employers of NY, 1964 November 16; 13.25 x 9.75, see # 775 (Object 179)
  - certificate, Chiropractic Association of NY, 1963 September 17; 14.75 x 11.75, see #s 243, 350; DEFRAMED (Object 181)
  - honorary State Chairman, USO, 12.75 x 12.5, see # 3; DEFRAMED (Object 182, Box 90)
  - certificate, Florida Institute of Technology Board of Assoc., 1969 January 15; 12.5 x 9.5, DEFRAMED (Object 182, Box 90)
  - honorary President, Rome Republican Teens Club, 1960 October 14; 8.75 x 10.75, DEFRAMED (Object 183, Box 90)
  - Certificate of Honorary Membership NY Press Club, 1963 January 17; 15 x 11.75, see # 22 for related; DEFRAMED (Object 184)
  - NAR w/ Nate Farbman, Ezequiel Padilla, Press Club in San Francisco, 1959 November 18; 11.5 x 14.5, penciled notes on back (Object 186)
  - NAR shaking hands with unidentified man and woman, 1958 June 30; 11.25 x 13.25, illegible signature on photo (Object 187, Box 90)
  - NAR w/ Ernie Davis, Jim Brown, signed, 1962; 12.75 x 14.5, DEFRAMED (Object 187, Box 90)
  - portrait of Henry A. Wallace, signed, 14.25 x 11 (Object 189)
  - portrait of Cordell Hull, signed, 14 x 10 (Object 190)
  - portrait of "Shorty", a young boy, 10 x 5.5 (Object 192)
  - voting ballot from Mt. Pleasant, 92nd Assembly, 36th Senate District, 1966 (Object 193)
  - Oscar C. Carr Philanthropy Award, National Council on Philanthropy, 1978 November 29 (Object 193)
  - New York Times front page: "Rockefeller Wins by 560,000 Margin", 1958 November 5 (Object 195)
  - NYT: "Rockefeller, Javits and Levitt Win", 1962 November 7 (Object 196)
  - NYT: "Rockefeller Wins", 1966 November 9 (Object 197)
  - NYT: "Rockefeller and Buckley Elected", 1970 November 4 (Object 198)
  - NYT: "Rockefeller is Resigning After 15 Years", 1973 December 12 (Object 199)
  - NYT: "Rockefeller Nominated by Ford as his Successor in VP", 1974 August 21 (Object 200)
  - NYT: "Rockefeller is Sworn in as Vice President", 1974 December 20 (Object 204)
  - memorial resolution, Republican National Committee, 1979 September 24 (Object 204)
    MEMORIAL
  - endorsement, Officers of Local Unions w/ NY Hotel & Motel Council (Object 205)
  - Honorary Mayorship, La Falla de la Plaza del Caudillo, 1959 March (Object 206)
  - copper plate etching about world peace "Novus Ordo Seclorum", 1968 (Object 207)
  - B&W portrait of FDR, inscribed "from his old friend" (Object 209)
  - photo of stairs in front of mural, 24.75 x 28.75 x 1.75 (Object 210)
  - collection of Asian decorative pieces in large frame, 37 x 17 (Object 210)
    MISCELLANEOUS ART
  - portrait by Hans E. V. Blyenburgh, to Margaretta Rockefeller 10/80, 24 x 20 (Object 212)
  - U.S. Senate resolution signed by NAR & 5 others, 1975 May 22; 17.25 x 24, see # 163 (Object 212)
  - NAR Center at SUNY Binghamton, 21 x 34.75 (Object 214)
  - portrait, poss. By Thomas Attarty, 1959; 31.5 x 25.75 (Object 215)
  - portrait, note "Best Wishes to Gov. from people of Warren County", 1966 August 31; 28.25 x 22.25 (Object 216)
  - NAR w/ others in "campaign spirit" painting by Al Young, 1967; 20.5 x 24.5 (Object 217)
  - NAR and Ford embracing, official White House photo, 20 x 24 (Object 218)
  - Joseph P. Wharton Award, Wharton Business School Club of NY, 1974 April 16; 30 x 22 (Object 218)
  - appt to National Study Commission from Nixon, 1973 March 15; 20.5 x 24.25 (Object 220)
  - appt as Under Secretary of Health, Education, Welfare by Pres. DDE, 1953 June 11; 20.5 x 24.25 (Object 221)
  - newspaper collage "Rock Signs Anti-Busing Bill", The Daily Argus, 1969 May 3; 25 x 19, DEFRAMED (Object 222)
    from residents of Mt. Vernon
  - Franklin Service Award, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, 1970 January 22; 21 x 17, see #s 159, 651 (Object 222)
  - political cartoon, from Charleston Gazette by W. VA campaigners, 1968 August; 18.75 x 15.25, see #s 145, 224; DEFRAMED (Object 224)
  - political cartoon, from Charleston Gazette by W. VA campaigners, 1968; 18.75 x 15.25, see #s 145, 223;DEFRAMED (Object 225)
  - NAR & family, LBJ, others at a White House ball, 12.25 x 16.25, DEFRAMED (Object 226)
  - appt as Special Assistant to the President, by DDE, 1954 December 16; 20.25 x 24 (Object 227)
  - Affirmation as Governor, from State Board of Canvassers, 1966 December 15; 21 x 26, see #s 12, 35, 138 (Object 228)
  - appt as member of Advisory Committee on Intergov. Relations, LBJ, 1965 November 10; 20.25 x 24.25 (Object 229)
  - appt as Chairman, President's Committee on Gov. Organization, DDE, 1953 January 24; 20 x 24 (Object 230)
  - poster "Ode to a Special, Special Asst", "Year of The Man", signed, 1955 December 31; 24.5 x 33.5 (Object 230)
  - plaque from John J. DeLury for Uniformed Sanitationmen's Assoc., 1964 September 3; 16 x 19.5 (Object 231)
  - Humanitarian Award, Luther E. Woodward School, 1966; 12 x 15 (Object 232, Box 43)
  - plaque for Outstanding Leadership, Route 17 Association, 1966 May 17; 9.5 x 12, see # 539 (Object 233, Box 7)
  - Herbert Hoover Award, National American Wholesale Grocers Assoc., 1976 March 16; 8 x 12 (Object 234, Box 6)
  - Merit Award, from Ruth Washington, Ruth Caston Mueller, Ethel Maddox, Cleo Hearnton Cook, Flora C. Grant, 1964 January 29; 8 x 12 (Object 235, Box 6)
  - Annual Merit Award, Evzone Chapter, Order of Ahepa, New Rochelle, 1970 June 19; 8 x 12 (Object 236, Box 6)
  - award, Boonville Fair Association, 1966 August 5; 8 x 10 (Object 237, Box 7)
  - cornerstone laying, Roswell Park Memorial Institute Cancer Drug Center, 1971 September 24; 5.25 x 8.25; item damaged. (Object 238, Box 27)
  - in thanks for childcare work, St. Vincent's Hall Inc, Brooklyn NY, 1969 November 25; 16 x 13.5 (Object 239)
  - Grass Roots Award for Bill 5478-B, Nassau County Press Assoc., 1970 October 4; 15 x 12 (Object 240, Box 11)
  - in thanks, Police Conference of NY Inc (box 11), 1961 May 22; 15x12, see #s 261, 456, 735, 260, 272, 364, 386, 514 (Object 241, Box 11)
  - tribute, Assoc. for the Help of Retarded Children, NYC Chapter, 1970 May 16; 14 x 12 (Object 242, Box 9)
  - tribute from Chiropractic Profession of NY in gold, mahogany, 1967 May 27; 13 x 11, see #s 180, 350 (Object 243, Box 5)
  - salute from Shrinedom, 81st Imperial Council Session, 1955 July 13; 12.5 x 9.5 (Object 244, Box 5)
  - award of merit, Black Republican Council of Texas, 1975 December 11; 12 x 9.5 (Object 245, Box 2)
  - tribute, from Mother African Methodist Episcopal Zion Church, 1970 March 8; 12 x 9, see # 546 (Object 246, Box 8)
  - Honorary Member, Herkimer County Fair Association, 1966 August 19; 12 x 9 (Object 247, Box 7)
  - Conservation & Water Management Award, Great Lakes Commission, 1970 September 24; 12 x 8.75 (Object 248, Box 7)
  - tribute, Inter-American Defense College, Ft. Lesley J. McNair, D.C., 1976 June 10; 10 x 10 (Object 249, Box 6)
  - in thanks for speech, Press Club of Metropolitan St. Louis, 1963 November 16; 11 x 7.75, see #22 for list (Object 250, Box 7)
  - tribute, Non-Sectarian Community Comm. Of United Jewish Appeal, 1966 March 9; 10 x 8, see #s 563, 583, 673, 817, 891 (Object 251, Box 7)
  - tribute, Caribbean Ready Group, Phibron Ten, 1969 July; 10 x 8 (Object 252, Box 7)
  - Equal Opportunity Award, Independent. Peoples Baptist Church of NYC, 1962 January 28; 9 x 7 (Object 253, Box 7)
  - letter inviting NY citizens to Mississippi Civil War Centennial, 1961; 15.5 x 11 (Object 254)
  - poem "The Conservationist" by Evans Estabrook, 12.25 x 9.5 (Object 255, Box 2)
  - Award of Merit, State Traffic Safety Council of NY, 1969 December 5; 10.5 x 12.25 (Object 256, Box 6)
  - tribute, Republican National Hispanic Assembly, 1976 July 29; 20 x 13 (Object 257, Box 5)
  - award, Help Addicts Voluntarily End Narcotics organization, 1967 May 6; 15 x 11 (Object 258, Box 5)
  - award, Hispanic Transit Society Inc, 1970 October 16; 15 x 12 (Object 259, Box 10)
  - honorary life membership, PBA of NY, 1962 October 29; 15.75 x 10.25, see #241 for list (Object 260, Box 10)
  - tribute for signing bills: Chap. 786, Chap.1000, Chap 545, from Police Conference of NYC Inc, 1967 May 15; 16 x 12, see # 241 (Object 261, Box 11)
  - B. Potoker Memorial Award, NYS Employees Brotherhood Committee Inc, 1968 February 8; 15 x 11 (Object 262, Box 5)
  - special citation, NYS Fire Fighters Association AFL-CIO, 1970 July 2; 15 x 10 (Object 263, Box 5)
  - award, Women's Forum of Nassau County, 1966 March 10; 12.5 x 10.25 (Object 264, Box 6)
  - award of merit, NJ Civil Defense Association, 1961 November 18; 12.25 x 10 (Object 265, Box 6)
  - Highway Achievement Award, NY Good Roads Association Inc, 1962 December; 10.75 x 10 (Object 267, Box 2)
  - plaque, 3rd Naval District, 11.5 x 9 (Object 267, Box 2)
    MISCELLANEOUS
  - anonymous plaque given at Governors'' Conference, made in Florida, missing central piece, 1963; 7.5 x 14.75, see #s 271,394,496,499,520,522, 524,555,601,602,727-729,806,808,883,977 (Object 268, Box 5)
  - honor from construction industry, Engineering News-Record, 1966 February 15; 10 x 8, see # 397 (Object 269, Box 2)
  - plaque, General Sun Yup Paik, Army Chief of Staff, Korea, 1957 July 15; 10.75 x 7 (Object 270, Box 2)
  - nameplate, Governors' Conference in Houston TX, 1972; 10.5 x 10, see #268 for list (Object 271, Box 2)
  - plaque, from Oswego Police Force, 1970 September 17; 9 x 7, see # 261 for list of related (Object 272, Box 12)
  - commemoration of visit, Australian American Festival, 1976 March 31; 7 x 6 (Object 273, Box 12)
  - statue of woman on horse, 20 x 16 (Object 275)
  - statue of woman on horse, 20 x 16 (Object 276)
  - painting of NAR "Fallout Shelters" by Maybelle L. N. Ekren, ND, 1960 April 12; 24 x 20, see #s 277-279, 325 (Object 277)
  - poster "Special Design to Reduce Impact, Fallout Shelter", 17 x 25, see #s 278, 279, 325 (Object 278)
  - poster "Special Design to Reduce Impact, Fallout Shelter", 17 x 22.75, see #s 277, 279, 325 (Object 279)
  - poster "Special Design to Reduce Impact, Fallout Shelter", 17 x 22.75, see #s 277, 278, 325 (Object 280)
  - optical illusion painting of circles with "74" and "76", 29.5 x 10.5 (Object 281)
  - Steve and Ann Marie Rockefeller, 22 x 15.5, DEFRAMED (Object 282)
  - statue of Buddha, 20.25 x 13.75 (Object 283)
  - woodcut print by Seong Moy "Homage to Lieou Poy", 1952; flat files (Object 284, Box 57)
  - resolution of gratitude, SUNY Board of Trustees, 1974 January 23; 15 x 11, in black slipcase (Object 284, Box 57)
  - 2 photos of 5 Rockefeller Brothers at conference table, & NAR at exhibit, 15 x 15, mounted on cardboard (Object 286, Box 90)
  - 11 photos of Seal Harbor, by S.C. Burden, in 2 folders, DEFRAMED (Object 286, Box 90)
  - copy of Ford's acceptance speech w/5 copies of NAR's speech, 1973 December-1974; DEFRAMED (Object 287, Box 90)
  - Good Scout Award, NY Council of Boy Scouts of America, 1972 February 17; see #122 for list; DEFRAMED (Object 288, Box 90)
  - NAR in parlor, by Dmitri Kessel for LIFE Magazine, 1958 August 19; 11 x 14, DEFRAMED (Object 290)
  - Sr. Pedro Leao Velleso of Pan American Union at dinner, 1945 March 12; 8 x 10, DEFRAMED (Object 291, Box 90)
  - Apolonio Sales, Minister of Agriculture, Brazil, signed w/ notes, 1944 July 9; 10 x 8, DEFRAMED (Object 291)
  - unidentified man, signed, 1943 January 14; 9.25 x 6.75, DEFRAMED (Object 293)
  - Richard Avedon portrait of NAR as VP, 1976; 13 x 11, DEFRAMED (Object 294, Box 90)
    w/ memo from studio
  - 2 copies of model rendering of Robert P. Young Village, DEFRAMED; see #318 (Object 294, Box 90)
  - certificate for distinguished service, Sigma Sigma Phi Grand Chapter, 1969 October 6; 8.5 x 11, see # 654; DEFRAMED (Object 295, Box 90)
  - certificate, National Press Club in DC, 1972 October 31; 9 x 12, see #22 for list; DEFRAMED (Object 296, Box 90)
  - tribute, from Governor's Festival of the Arts, WA, 1966; 14 x 10.75, DEFRAMED (Object 298, Box 57)
  - poem "Our Next President", by Royal White, 14.5 x 12 (Object 298, Box 57)
  - scriptmaster (for holding speeches) w/ seal of VP (Object 299, Box 54)
  - sketch of Mrs. NAR, 16.5 x 14, DEFRAMED (Object 301)
  - ink drawing of NAR by Sid L. Hydeman, 20 x 15 (Object 302)
  - "Carter's Grove" painting, 16 x 20 (Object 303)
  - decree, Touchdown Club of New York, signed, 1970 September 23; 18 x 13.25, DEFRAMED (Object 304)
  - cartoon by C.D. Batchelor, signed and inscribed, 1959; 27.25 x 21.25, very messy (Object 305)
  - cartoon by Hani Glass from The Standard-Times, MA, w/ copy, 16.5 x 14, DEFRAMED (Object 306)
  - cartoon by David Roby of Auburn Prison, signed & inscribed, 1971 September 2; 28 x 22 (Object 307)
  - portrait, by Coythe Debany, 1961; 20 x 15 (Object 308)
  - portrait by Soraci, 23.75 x 18, DEFRAMED (Object 309)
  - 2 watercolor portraits by Florence E. Donahue, 1968; 24.75 x 22, 22 x 17.75 (Object 310)
  - Pan Am World Map, from Pan American Clipper Club, 18 x 32, see #116 (Object 311)
  - 7 collage pages about White House conference "To Fulfill These Rights," summaries of official report, 1966; stored together in manila envelope (Object 312)
  - 3 anti-drug advertising posters, 26 x 23, 26 x 21, 23.5 x 18.5 (Object 314)
  - honorary lifetime membership, NYS Council for the Arts, 11 x 12, DEFRAMED (Object 315)
  - drawing of a couple, possibly by Holocaust survivor Yehuda Bakon, 18.5 x 14 (Object 316, Box 91)
  - honorary citizen, Dallas TX, 1974 February 21; 12 x 9, DEFRAMED; see #19, 84 (Object 316, Box 90)
  - NAR w/ group in front of plane, signed illegibly, 1975 April; 9.5 x 11.5 (Object 318)
  - 2 copies, road plans for Robert R. Young village, 19.5 x 17.75, 16.25 x 17.25, see # 294 (Object 319)
  - Order of Merit, President of the Italian Republic, 1961 October 13; 16.5 x 12.25, DEFRAMED (Object 320)
  - cartoon by Hy Rosen, signed & inscribed, 1972 December 3; 11.75 x 14.5, see # 144; DEFRAMED (Object 321)
  - appt to Mayor's Business Advisory Committee, from LaGuardia, 1940 May 27; 15.5 x 19, DEFRAMED (Object 322)
  - portrait of Happy by Wallace Bradley, w/ news clipping, 1967 June 9; 16 x 16, signed from Louise and Paul (Object 323)
  - Nixon in Albany, reprints from the Courier and Chatham Courier, 1968 October; 20 x 16, 11 x 8.5, DEFRAMED (Object 324)
  - abstract painting of woman, signed & inscribed by Endokia, 1961 November 23; 24 x 18 (Object 325)
  - designs for fallout shelters, 19.25 x 28.5, see #s 276-279 (Object 326, Box 48)
  - appt to Advisory Committee on Intergovernmental Relations, LBJ, 1967 November 10; 19 x 23 (Object 326, Box 48)
  - honorary doctorate, Pace College, 1970 October 21; 11 x 14, see #454 (Object 327, Box 48)
  - amendments, to change name of Museum of Indigenous Art to the Museum of Primitive Art, w/ writs from NYS Education Dept, 1956 December; 8.5x11, 16x20, 16x20, stored together in tube (Object 328, Box 48)
  - National Award, West Side Association. of Commerce of NYC, 1969 November 13; 18 x 14 (Object 329, Box 48)
  - 3 sketches for presentation of statue, 1949 October; 16.25 x 10.75 (Object 330, Box 50)
  - certificate, NY Civil Service Employees Assoc, w/ signatures, 1966 September 16; 35 x 23, see #402 (Object 331, Box 50)
  - honorary doctorate, University of Los Andes, 1969 May 28; 14.25 x 18.75 (Object 332, Box 50)
  - honorary doctorate, Ithaca College, 1970 May 16; 14 x 16.75, see #466 (Object 333, Box 50)
  - poster, Arts & Entertainment Committee for campaign team, 1970; 24 x 20, see #334,402,442,490,492,548,549, 736, 849, 886-889,907,918,953,954,956-958 (Object 334, Box 47)
  - petition for funds, Pre-K program in NY, w/ signatures, glitter, etc, 1970 December 17; 52.5 x 27.75 (Object 335, Box 47)
  - blueprints for Yoshimuro house in Pocantico Hills, 1972 September 27 (Object 336, Box 49)
  - print of mountains, from Palmer Hoyt, The Denver Post, 1970 December; 19.75 x 24.75 (Object 337, Box 49)
  - signed poster from crew of Apollo 13, 35 x 23.5, fragile, see #438 (Object 338, Box 49)
  - print of Glen Riddle's Man o' War, possibly by Milton Menasco, 1968; 26 x 32 (Object 339, Box 49)
  - illustration of Jewish Wedding on scroll, by Ay Arkin, 1971; 35.25 x 24 (Object 340, Box 49)
  - poster from Bicentennial celebrations in Philadelphia, 28 x 22 (Object 341, Box 84)
  - petition against budget cuts, Clara Barton Vocational High School, 138 x 36, 3 large rolls w/ some 600 signatures (Object 342, Box 51)
  - petition against budget cuts, Cortland College students & faculty, large roll of signatures; damaged. (Object 343, Box 51)
  - bizarre hand drawn poster w/ Howard Hughes, rockets, etc, 1969 July 10; 28 x 22 (Object 344, Box 49)
  - plaque to NAR & wife from Albert Einstein College, Yeshiva Univ., 1953; 21.5 x 17, see #s 103, 465, 594, 869 (Object 345)
  - Harry S. Truman Good Neighbor Award, Kansas City MI, 1978 May 8; 25 x 16 (Object 346)
  - plaque, National Remodelers Association, NY Council, 1967 September 19; 18 x 14 (Object 347)
  - tribute, from the business and residents of East Harlem, 1974 January 3; 16 x 13 (Object 348)
  - award, Junior Achievement National Business Leadership Conference, 1975 January 23; 17 x 13.75, wood base is damaged. (Object 349)
  - Humanitarian Award, P.J. Cerasoli Chiropractic Foundation Inc, 1963 November 9; 14 x 17, see #s 180, 243 (Object 350)
  - Keystone Award, Flatbush Chapter, Boys Clubs of America, 1966 April 21; 14 x 12, see #587 (Object 351, Box 3)
  - Thomas F. Cunningham Award, International House, New Orleans, 1964 April 21; 14 x 11 (Object 352, Box 4)
  - Commander in Chief seal of NY Navy, NY Naval Militia, 1967; 12 x 9 (Object 353, Box 1)
  - 2nd Annual Award, Brazilian-American Chamber of Commerce Inc, 1971 May 13; 12 x 9 (Object 354, Box 4)
  - tribute, Legion of Voters Inc for Puerto Rican Community, 1965 July 16; 15 x 11 (Object 355, Box 3)
  - tribute, Grand Lodge NYS Sons of Italy in America, 1970 October 3; 15 x 12, damaged. (Object 356, Box 4)
  - special award, Empire State Rescue & 1st Aid Association, 1955-64; 12 x 9 (Object 357, Box 1)
  - Human Rights Award, Joint American Jewish Committee and the Anti-defamation League of B'Nai B'rith, 1959 September 22; 11 x 9.5, see #751 (Object 358, Box 4)
  - leadership award, National Assoc. of State Drug Abuse Programs, 1973; 10 x 15 (Object 359, Box 3)
  - tribute, Oswego County Civil War Centennial Committee, 1962 October 6; 12 x 12 (Object 360, Box 3)
  - tribute, Operation Amigo Club, Miami-Dad Junior College, 1969-1970; 12 x 10 (Object 361, Box 1)
  - Man of the Year, Camp Montebello for blind children, NY, 1970; 12 x 9 (Object 362, Box 1)
  - Service Award, Construction Specifications Institute, 1973 June 25; 12 x 9 (Object 363, Box 1)
    for creating NYS Council on Architecture
  - Golden Rule Award, St. George Assoc. & Police Dept of NYC, 1971 May 2; 13 x 11, see #261 (Object 364, Box 3)
  - Honorary Foreman, Endicott Johnson Glendale Plant, 1969 January 29; 12.5 x 10 (Object 365, Box 1)
  - State of Israel Bonds, for understanding/supporting Middle East, 1959 June 24; 12.5x8.5 (Object 366, Box 1)
    given at Long Island Leadership Dinner
  - plaque, Lincoln Day Dinner, Columbia County Young Republicans, 1968; 12 x 9 (Object 367, Box 1)
  - tribute, 3rd Reserve Recruiting, U.S. Navy, 1972 October 11; 12 x 8 (Object 368, Box 1)
  - membership, King David Club, El Al Israel Airlines, 8.75 x 11.25, stored w/key, pin, box, tags, card, etc (Object 369, Box 45)
  - Humanitarian Award, United Cerebral Palsy of NYC, 1971 October 14; 9.25x11, folds into picture frame, see #s 426,748 (Object 370, Box 36)
  - portrait in relief, 12" diameter (Object 371, Box 4)
  - plaque from dedication of Kodak Marketing Education Center, 1971 May 11; 11 x 15 (Object 372, Box 4)
  - plaque from groundbreaking for Yeshiva Flatbush High School, 1961 June; 6 x 12 (Object 373, Box 1)
  - Appreciation Award, North Austin Optimists, Austin TX, 1975; 10 x 7 (Object 374, Box 7)
  - in appreciation for services to U.S. Government, from B.S.A.C., 1976; 9 x 7 (Object 375, Box 7)
  - in appreciation, Dallas Council on World Affairs, 1974 February 21; 7.75 x 7.75 (Object 376, Box 7)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebrations, NY Academy of Sciences, 1967; 7 x 5 (Object 377, Box 7)
  - Paul H. Hoch MD 1902-1964, 6.5 x 4.5 (Object 378, Box 7)
  - ceramic turbine rotor, from Malcolm R. Currie DDR & E, 1976 August; 11 x 7 (Object 379, Box 8)
  - tribute, Jacyee, Tri-Action Day, Salem Oregon, 1964 February 8; 3 x 4 (Object 380, Box 4)
  - tribute from Square Deal Republican Club, for people of Harlem, 1960 October 29; 22 x 15 (Object 381)
  - Man of the Year, Young Israel Synagogue of Manhattan, 1971 January 16; 16 x 14 (Object 382)
  - Citizen of the University Award, Alumni Association of SUNY Albany, 1978 May 20; 16 x 13 (Object 383)
  - citation & plaque, NY Water Pollution Control Association, 1973; 16x12, 6x4, damaged, stored separately (Object 384, Box 43)
  - citation & plaque, NY Water Pollution Control Association (Object 384)
  - 1st Annual Public Service Award, NY Jewish Veterans of USA, 1969 February 4; 15 x 12.5 (Object 385, Box 11)
  - tribute, NYS Association of Chiefs of Police, 1970 July 29; 15 x 12.5, see #261 for related (Object 386, Box 9)
  - Pierre Award, Westchester County Recreation and Parks Services, 1971 May; 12 x 10 (Object 387, Box 8)
  - tribute, Business and Professional Women's Clubs, 1965 May 18; 15 x 10.5 (Object 388, Box 10)
  - Distinguished Service Award, Howard Law Alumni Association of DC, 1975 April 9; 12 x 9 (Object 389, Box 8)